- Cheers.     - Cheers.
You look cute in bubbles.
Ahh, you're just all liquored up.
Hey, it's me. I'm coming in.
I've had a very long, hard day.
Want some chicken?
No, thanks. No chicken. Bye-bye.
You sure? Some extra-crispy, dirty rice?
For the last time, no! Get out, Joey!
All right.
Are you okay? He wouldn't leave.
He kept asking me if I wanted chicken.
Chicken?
I could eat some chicken.
Hey, Joe!
Could I get a, uh, three-piece, some coleslaw, some beans and a Coke?
Aah! Diet Coke.
- Hey.     - Hey.
- Morning, Pheebs.     - I have to tell you this story.
I was coming over and this cabdriver...
Was his name Angus?
What?
He was a cabdriver we had in London.
Oh. Ha, ha, ha.
All right. Anyway...
What was that pub he took us to?
The Wheat Sheaf!
And they had that beer...
- Boddington's.     - Boddington's.
Ooh, uh, Pheebs was going to tell a story.
So he had a really funny hat.
I don't want to talk about it.
- Hey.     - Hey, Ross!
Boddington's!
Oh, man!
I'd walk back to London for another frosty one of those bad boys.
They have them at the British pub by the Trade Center.
Later!
Shouldn't Rachel be back?
Her plane got delayed.
But she should be here by now.
So you talked to her? Did she sound mad?
No. But she likes me.
You abandoned her on a plane to Greece.
I did not "abandon" Rachel. Okay?
Emily showed up at the airport.
I had to go after her. I did what I had to do.
She's my wife. Rachel is my wife.
Emily!
Emily is my wife.
Man, what is that?
You haven't heard from Emily?
Not since I lost her at the airport.
I can't believe she can outrun you.
Hey! She's fast, okay?
You think you can beat me? Let's go! Outside!
Hi!
Hi! Rachel!
Rach, I am so sorry. I am so, so sorry.
Come on. You just did what you had to do.
Hi, Pheebs.
That's it? You're not mad? It must've been terrible.
Terrible? Hell, I was in Greece!
There was a nice hotel, nice beach, met the nice people.
It's not too shabby for Rachel.
So, what, that's it?
Well, yeah. We're cool. Totally cool.
Thanks, Rach. You're the best.
Oh, no. You're the best.
Oh, I got to go to the flower store.
No one will tell me where Emily is...
...so I'm sending 72 long-stemmed, red roses to her parents' house.
One for each day I've known and loved her.
That should get her talking.
When you make out the card, be sure to make it out to "Emily."
It's good that you had such a good time in Greece.
What?
I didn't have a good time in Greece!
Ross abandoned me!
I couldn't get a plane out. I had to stay in their suite!
People came up to me going, "Mrs. Geller! Why are you cry?"
I mean, it was so humiliating!
I felt like such an idiot!
It's all my fault. You know why?
Because I make very bad decisions.
Oh, that's not true.
Yes, it is true. I went after Ross in stupid London!
London is stupid! Stupid!
I should've never gone to London.
From now on, you make all my decisions for me.
Oh, no. I did that for someone once.
I'm not comfortable having that power over someone's life.
I'll do it.
Fine. Monica, you are now in charge of my love life.
Okay. I got to go to work.
And, uh, Rachel, great to have you back.
Pheebs!
Always a pleasure.
Rachel? Sweetie, look.
Here's a cute picture of you and Joey.
He's married.
Ross is married. I still can't believe it.
Honey, sweetie, by the edges.
I'll just have to accept it.
I mean, it's my fault.
Edges! Fingers! Smudgy!
Oh, my God!
That's okay. I know that you're very upset right now.
I know that wasn't about me.
I bet it was about her a little.
If you'd stop thinking about Ross...
...you'd notice there are great guys everywhere.
Look. Gunther.
He's nice. He's cute.
Yeah. I guess Gunther is...
What about that guy over there?
That's the guy you flirted with at the counter.
Oh, I don't know. I don't know.
You're going to talk to him.
I make your decisions, and I say you're going to talk to him.
All right.
You're the boss. I got to do what you tell me.
Say that to him, and you're golden.
- Hey.     - Hey.
Hey, Pheebs. We got our pictures back from London.
Here's all of us at the Tower of London...
Here we all are.
There's Ross and Joey and you and...
And me.
We've been talking about London too much.
Sorry, it's just because I couldn't be there.
All I get to do now is pregnant stuff. It bums me out.
- I'm sorry.     - Sorry.
- What happened?     - A little of this, a little of that.
I got myself a date tomorrow.
See? Didn't I tell you? You're getting over Ross already.
Get out.
What took so long?
I got caught up at work. But I'm quitting tomorrow.
So thanks for having me over.
Rach...
Pheebs...
See you, man.
What the hell was that?
Probably some European goodbye thing he picked up in London.
That's not European.
It felt French.
I really had a good time.
Yeah, me too.
- So...     - So...
I guess this is it.
Yeah, um...
- Unless you want to come inside?     - Yeah!
Oh, uh, wait a minute. You know what? I can't decide this.
Okay. Just hold on a second.
Um, hi.
Hi.
Where's Monica? I have to ask her something.
Doing her laundry.
What's that?
It came in the mail today.
It's 72 long-stemmed, red roses.
One for each day I've known and loved Emily...
...cut up into mulch.
Honey, that's awful.
It's not so bad.
Monica's going to make potpourri.
I think I'm going to go wander out in the rain for a while.
It's not raining.
I can't catch a break.
You're not going anywhere. Sit right here.
I'll make you some tea and we'll talk this out.
All right?
Okay.
- Hey, Dave.     - Yeah.
Um, I need to take a rain check. My roommate is really sick.
Okay. Bye.
Honey, listen.
I know things seem so bad...
...and that they won't get any...
Could I talk to you?
I dropped some socks.
Yeah.
What is the matter with you? Do you want to fall into the trap?
You did not drop any socks!
I saw Dave, and he said you blew him off!
You listen to me!
I'm calling the shots! I say you leave Ross and go get Dave.
What are you doing?
Well, ultimately I was trying, you know, I wanted...
...to tell him that I'm still in love with him.
What? You cannot tell him that!
Why? Why not?
People love to hear that!
I make the decisions and I say no!
You know what? No, you don't make my decisions, because...
...you're fired.
You can't fire me.
I make your decisions, and I say I'm not fired. Ha!
Well...
Rachel! Come on, let me in!
Having some trouble?
Rachel locked the door.
I'll kick that door in if you give me some sugar.
Rachel! Let me in!
Thank you.
Rachel? Can I talk to you outside for a sec?
No.
We really need to talk.
Well, then talk.
Okay, I will.
Remember that thing we just discussed that you wanted to do?
Yes.
What thing?
Rachel wants to take swing dance lessons.
Which I think is a really stupid idea.
It's dangerous. She won't get what she wants.
And who knows who she might end up hurting?
Monica's right. Swing dancing can be tricky.
I have to use the phone.
I got to cancel those five, giant teddy bears I sent to Emily.
My God. Think of the massacre.
I'm going to do it.
I know you think I'm crazy.
But before you tell him, try to find one person...
...who thinks it's a good idea. I bet you can't.
Please?
All right. Fine.
Joey! I'm in!
All right. Good deal.
Pheebs! Hey!
Uh, Pheebs?  Yeah?
Um, you know how you were saying you didn't get to go to London...
...and you were feeling left out?     - Yeah.
Well, we all felt really bad about that...
...so we decided to take a little trip together.
Oh, that's so nice!
How great! Where's the trip?
- Well, we thought we would all go to a picnic...
...in Central Park!     - Central Park?
All of us. All day.
That sucks!
That's not a trip! I just came from there.
What'll we high-five about at the stupid park?
It's right by my house. All right!
I'm going home to bask in the triumph of my Central Park idea.
Hold on a sec there, Mr. Kissy.
I wanted to talk to you about...
...this whole new European thing you've got going on.
And I need to say it makes me very uncomfortable...
...and I just, you know, just stop it!
Just bringing some culture to the group.
That's fine. Just don't bring it in my mouth.
It makes me want to puke.
Hey, everybody! Pheebs is here!
Phoebe! Whoo!  Okay. Whoo! Hi!
Pheebs, we decided that the picnic idea was a little...
It didn't have any... Well, it blew.
We thought that this afternoon we'd all go away for the whole weekend...
...to Atlantic City.
Ooh, Atlantic City! Oh, that's a great plan! Whose plan was that?
Mine!
- Wait. It was my plan.     - No...
...I said we needed a new plan.
And I came up with Atlantic City.
Which is the new plan.
Why don't we, um, all meet upstairs in an hour?
Okay.
I'm going to go pack. I'm going to go pack my ass off.
Let's go.
You know what? I'll meet you in a minute.
Rachel, you didn't find anyone, so you can't tell him.
You know what? That doesn't matter.
Do you know how painful it is to tell someone you love them...
...and not have them say it back?
I don't care.
Okay...
I can't watch.
What you reading?
Paper.
Yeah? What's it about?
The events from around the globe.
Okay...
Uh, there's something I have to talk to you about.
Everyone's saying I shouldn't.
But I think they're wrong. People can be wrong.
Once at work...
...I thought carbon dating is fossilized...
I'm really trying to tell you something here.
Yeah...
Go ahead.
I think I'm just going to say it.
I'm just going to say it.
Uh...
I'm still in love with you, Ross.
Wow, uh...
Huh. I'm...
Wow. I'm not sure what to do with that right now.
What? Was that a joke? Because it's mean.
I'm so dead serious.
I'm totally serious.
Why are you laughing?
Because I just heard it!
I heard it! And it's ridiculous!
I mean...
You're married!
You're married, and it's just ridiculous.
When I said it, I sort of floated up out of my body.
And then I heard myself say it, and then the floating Rachel...
I was like, "You are such an idiot!"
- Well, I am married.     - I know.
Though I haven't spoken to her since the wedding.
I'm sorry. That's not funny.
Actually, it kind of is.
My wife won't return my calls.
I don't know where my wife is.
"Hey, Ross! Where's the missus?" "Don't know!"
Oh, God.
Okay.
You know what? Could you forget I told you this?
Well, I kind of have to.
Because the thing is...
The thing is, you know, that you're married to Emily.
That is what the thing is.
Oh, God.
Things won't be weird between us, right? Was that stupid?
Me telling you that?
No, no. I'm glad you did.
If nothing else...
...it's always great when someone tells you they love you.
That's what I said!
- Thank you for being so nice.     - No. Thank you for...
Thank you.
- Okay, let's go!     - Yeah, Atlantic City!
Come on!
Atlantic City, baby!
Let's roll some bones. Hey, Joey!
High-five for rolling bones.
- Ow!     - Ow!
Oh.
Ooh!
Uh, Pheebs, you're leaking.
Oh, my God. Your water broke.
Oh! Okay!
Well, don't worry. I call shotgun.
Pheebs, we have to take you to the hospital now.
Pheebs, the babies are coming now.
Honey! High-five! The babies are coming!
Whoo!
Remember when my water broke?
Phoebe's going to have her babies.
I know. It's beautiful and amazing.
I had to kiss Phoebe and Rachel every time I left the room.
It's too bad they didn't see us having sex.
Do you know anything about women?
No.
- It's all right.     - Okay.